So I'm not sure if you all have been keeping up with what's going on in Texas, but Democratic
State Representative Nicole Collier has currently been kidnapped because she is being prevented
from leaving the Texas State House unless she agrees to being monitored by Texas law
enforcement.
No, she literally spent the night in the House.
As we know, the Democrats left the state last week and refused to return to create a quorum,
which is the amount of people needed in order for a vote to be legitimate.
They did not want to create a quorum because the vote was to create redistricting in Texas.
What does Texas have to do with me, Amanda?
This redistricting would create five new seats in districts that they have chopped and screwed
in how they drew it up in order to ensure that it would go to Republicans.
These new seats would create five new members of the House of Representatives, thus increasing
the probability for there to be a higher Republican MAGA fascist majority in the House of Representatives
in the midterms.
So even if you're not in Texas, this matters to you.
I know a lot of people get confused and frustrated at how all these different state things affect
us on a federal level.
But here is a great example.
And Nicole Collier is actually doing what I'm always pleading with our Democrats to do,
which is demonstrating being a public servant.
She is representing right now.
She's putting her body on the line for a legitimate stance that says, absolutely not.
We will not go along with the Republicans.
And we have seen too many Democrats do the opposite.
So we stand with you, Nicole Collier, and shout to all of the people who have already been
arrested trying to protest and get her out of there.
Well, turns out, apparently, if I understand correctly from the Texans in my comments, she
and other Democrats returned because they had to get their paychecks because the Republicans
made it so that their payments could only be done in paper checks and not direct deposit.
And so they returned, which ended up creating a quorum in order to get their checks.
There are actually Democrat representatives who have yet to return.
So I'm going to go on and have to rescind all of that.
But it is, there is something to be said for her trying to right that wrong by doing this.
But damn, there's always an M-Tams.